<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Irene Ong</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Irene Ong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:53:22 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about me.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:40:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Irene Ong and I’m pursing a Comp Rhet English degree with a Computer Science minor. While these two may seem like an unlikely pairing, they made sense to me. I came to the United States in 1998 as an enormous, chubby baby. (My parents dragged me here without asking.) I grew up with one of those classic fat desktop computers and I was a gaming maniac. I learned to code in high school and naturally, when it came time to choose my path in college, I would choose computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somebody TV Program Team Translation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/somebody/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:53:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/somebody/</guid>
      <description>Background I joined a translation team during the summer of 2020 to provide English subtitles for a Korean television program called &amp;ldquo;Somebody&amp;rdquo;. We operate on a two week release schedule. I am a part of the translators team where my duties include translating 30 to 45 minute segments of each episode and working with typesetters to resolve any issues. Our team has provided English subtitles for episodes 7-9 of season one and we are currently working through season two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Actress Gong Hyojin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/gong-hyojin-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:53:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/gong-hyojin-interview/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this translation assignment for a Literary and Media Translation class I took at Ewha Womans University in Seoul, South Korea. This was the final project for the class. I was tasked with providing English translations and subtitles for any video clip of my choice. I learned how to use Aegisub subtitling software for this project.
You can view the translation script and final subtitled video at this folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary You Drama Clip</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/extraordinary-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:52:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/extraordinary-you/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this translation assignment for a Literary and Media Translation class I took at Ewha Womans University in Seoul, South Korea. I was tasked with transcribing a Korean video clip and providing an English translation.
To view this work, see the PDF Version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Guest by Kim Youngha Excerpt</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/the-last-guest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/the-last-guest/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this translation assignment for a Literary and Media Translation class I took at Ewha Womans University in Seoul, South Korea. The commision requirements were to take a foreignization approach and maintain Korean cultural references in popular fiction. The original text comes from at short story titled &amp;ldquo;The Last Guest&amp;rdquo; by Kim Youngha. I translated the text from Korean to English.
To view this work, see the PDF Version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiderman Comic Excerpt</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/spidermancomic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:52:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/spidermancomic/</guid>
      <description>I completed this translation assignment for a Literary and Media Translation class I took at Ewha Womans University in Seoul, South Korea. I was tasked with providing an English to Korean translation of the Spider Comic vol 11.
To view this translation, see the PDF Version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snotgirl Comic Excerpt</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/snotgirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:51:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/translation/snotgirl/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this translation assignment for a Literary and Media Translation class I took at Ewha Womans University in Seoul, South Korea. The commision was to provide a viable commercial English to Korean translation applying domesticization techniques. I translated an excerpt from the SnotGirl Comic Issue #12.
You can view the original excerpt, final translation, and translator&amp;rsquo;s note at this folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSC 3210: Computer Organization and Programming</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/csc3210/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:49:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/csc3210/</guid>
      <description>Background This page is under construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSC 4740: Data Mining</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/csc4740/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 10:47:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/csc4740/</guid>
      <description>Background This page is under construction. I am currently taking this class and I will update this when the semester ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 3120: Digital Writing &amp; Publication</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3120/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:38:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3120/</guid>
      <description>Background I created this website during Spring 2020 for Professor George Pullman’s ENGL 3120 Digital Writing and Publication course. Digital writing differs significantly from traditional forms of writing. I learned how to navigate and structure content for digital landscapes. For this project, I was given the opportunity to create a website that I can use to display my portfolio. This website is aimed for the English department instructors who will evaluate my senior portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 4201: Revolution, Race, Gender, and the Institutionalization of Oppression</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl4201/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:36:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl4201/</guid>
      <description>Background This page is under construction. I am currently taking this class and I will update this when the semester ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 4320: Senior Seminar in Rhetoric and Composition</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl4320/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:36:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl4320/</guid>
      <description>Background This page is under construction. I am currently taking this class and I will update this when the semester ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 3110: Technical Writing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3110/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:35:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3110/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this marketing kit project during Fall 2018 for Professor Baotong Gu’s ENGL 3110 Technical Writing course. I was given the opportunity to work with a group to produce a technical writing document for a real client. My group decided to create a marketing kit for Lime’s Juicer program. Our marketing kit included a flyer to promote the position and an informational brochure with in-depth information on the position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 3140: Editing for Publication</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3140/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:35:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3140/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this editorial project during Spring 2019 for Professor Reiner Smolinski’s ENGL 3140 Editing for Publication course. I was tasked with transcribing a given historical piece of writing and modernizing it. Once I had a good understanding of the writing, I created a diplomatic transcription of the work, then modernized that transcription and constructed a style sheet for my modernized transcription. Through this project, I acquired an exhaustive amount of copyediting principles and publication practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 3050: Intro to Rhetoric and Composition</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3050/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:34:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3050/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this annotated bibliography during Fall 2018 for Professor Michael Harker’s ENGL 3050 Intro to Rhetoric and Composition course. I learned most of the fundamentals of rhetoric in this this class. For this assignment, I was tasked with finding sources and annotating them for a rhetorical analysis paper. I chose to analyze the rhetorical devices used in advertising used in podcasts. This work would be useful for podcasters who want to understand how to appeal to their audiences while satisfying their sponsers’ requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 3100: Composition Studies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3100/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 14:34:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3100/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this research paper during Spring 2020 for Professor Nathan Wagner’s ENGL 3100 Composition Studies course. For this assignment, I was tasked with crafting an argument about an aspect of composition studies. I used the readings we discussed over the semester and outside sources I found on my own to create an argument about the practice of composition studies, or more specifically why and how to incorporate digital learning into English pedagogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGL 3105: Practical Grammar</title>
      <link>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3105/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 21:14:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/portfolio/writing/engl3105/</guid>
      <description>Background I completed this revision project during Spring 2019 for Professor Melissa McLeod’s ENGL 3105 Practical Grammar course. This course gave me a refresher on grammar principles I already knew and it also helped me put a name to certain principles that I knew intuitively, but didn’t know the technical term for. I was tasked with revising an older paper written for one of my past English courses using the grammar principles we reviewed and learned over the course of the semester.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
